Apparently, my Amazon reviews go back to
2014 when I bought this lotion bottle.
One star. Didn't last long enough. And
the image I added was this. Next review,
we have a single spoon. Wow. Okay,
that's a lot of text. I still gave it
five stars, though. It must have been a
good spoon. Next review. You got to
believe me, I did not buy this. Okay,
it's these leggings. Four stars. My
husband loved these. And this is when I
realized something dark. This is my
family account. And what my little
cousin Nolan purchased is really
concerning. One star. Do not wear this
to school. Everyone calls me chunky now.
Two stars. Finally, an earplug to block
out mom and dad's fighting. Seems
Nolan's really going through it, right?
Well, just check this out. This made me
feel confident. Can't wait to take out
my crush. Five stars. Nolan is finally
getting somewhere. Or is he? I purchased
this product for me and my crush. Turns
out she cheated on me. I'm broken. Three
stars. But the final arc of Nolan's
reviews has one more. Starting with five
stars. Nice, creamy, and smooth. And he
attached an image here.
>> [screaming]